my-adserver.com 2012-03-24

# HD Marketing | Targeted Traffic now !

HD Marketing delivers interstitial advertisements across a network of sites, which ranges from major web brands as well as smaller specialty sites. 

Use standard ad units, like banners or try our full page interstitial ads. 

  1. Our Commitment

HD Marketing (HDM) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement outlines the types of information we gather when you use HD-marketing.com services, as well as the steps we take to keep that information safe.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

  2. Information Collected and How It's Used    

    * Your IP address

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is automatically assigned to your computer every time you establish a connection on the Internet. HD-marketing.com uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. When you open an account on HD-marketing.com, your ip address will be associated with personally identifiable information.

    * Cookies

In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to store your account number once you register. We never use cookies to capture or contain personal information from your computer. The only personal information HD-marketing.com has is what you give to us.

    * Third Party Cookies

From time to time we employ the services of a third party agent in tracking statistical data on the Site. This agent may utilize cookies and web beacons to facilitate the service. A web beacon is a 1x1 image that tracks site traffic and isn't tied to any personal information. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over these third party cookies. We use this aggregated information to improve our Site functionality.

    * Third Party Links

Please note in the privacy statement that your Site contains links to third party sites. HD Marketing is not responsible for the information practices of these sites, and users' are encouraged to read their privacy policies prior to disclosing personal information.

    * Your Account

In order to utilize certain services, you may be asked to provide certain personal information to HDM, such as account information (user name and password), credit card information (card type, account number, expiration date, and billing address), banking information (Swift/ABA routing number, account number, bank name and address), PayPal email, email address, IM user ID, name and company name, tax identification number, and home or work address and telephone number, as well as certain demographic information, including city, state, country and zip code. HDM uses your personal information to deliver the services you have requested and to communicate with you, including certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. All such information is provided voluntarily by you. No such information is utilized by HDM for the purpose of displaying targeted websites or profiling. HDM does not sell, rent or lease such information to third parties.

    * Additional Information Collected

Any personal correspondence you send to us, including e-mail and letters about your activities or postings pertaining to HD-marketing.com, and all entries made by you onto our site may be collected and stored. Any notes, ideas, suggestions, or other material submitted by Users becomes the property of HD-marketing.com.

    * Children Under 13 Years of Age

In light of the concern over protecting children's privacy online, HD Marketing Agency does not knowingly request, collect, or share personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. Our websites, products and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children.

    * Expunging Your Information from Our Records

You may use the contact form on HD-marketing.com or use one of the alternate contact methods listed below to remove your contact information from our database provided we have completed all your pending transactions. Please note, however, that information is never completely removed from our history and disaster recovery archives.

  3. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties    

    * Personal Information

HD-marketing.com does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties in ways that are not disclosed in the privacy statement. If we were to ever do so, you will have the opportunity to opt-out beforehand.

    * Transactional Information

HD-marketing.com transactional information such as traffic patterns, sales, aggregate data regarding general shopping patterns, and other site information may be shared with vendors and other reputable third parties. This data will never contain any identifiable personal information of HD-marketing.com users. For example, we might share statistics on how many customers purchased a specific product, but we will not specifically disclose who purchased the product.

    * Billing Information

We use Optimal Payments to provide credit card billing on our site. When you sign up for HD-marketing.com, we will share your credit card information email and billing address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

    * Legal Issues

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

  4. Unsolicited Contact & Communication

HD Marketing Agency will not sell, rent, or disclose any of the contact information we have collected from you to third parties, except as described in this document (see Disclosure of Information to Third Parties).

We, however, may occasionally wish to communicate with our customers in order to provide them with information relevant to the services we provide or the management of their accounts. This might include newsletters, or notices of new services or offers from HD-marketing.com. In addition, we will provide clients with their initial activation and welcome email, service and system updates, account and balance warnings, confirmation emails, and quality approval notifications.

As part of our service, our Customer Service Department routinely communicates with members by phone o r email to respond to questions or issues relating to their account, or to offer optimization services. We may also solicit some of our clients from time to time, either online or by email, to participate in client surveys. Participation in these surveys is voluntary, and the information collected provides HD Marketing Agency with valuable feedback on our services, which in turn, helps us to improve them.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by **contacting us**. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications from the members area, or you may contact us using the contact information listed below.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

  5. Safety and Security

After we receive the data at HD-marketing.com, it is stored on a secure server and cannot be accessed from outside the company. All data is secure and is protected from alteration, loss or misuse. The HD-marketing.com employees who process your order are the only people with access to your personal information. All HD-marketing.com employees sign a privacy/security policy agreement, which provides legal confidentiality protections for all HD-marketing.com users. Any violation of this policy results in disciplinary action, including possible termination, criminal prosecution, and civil action.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), the information you provide is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, you will know that you are on a secure page because the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer is in its locked form, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, protect all user-information off-line. For example, all of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is subject to restricted use in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

  6. Your Consent

By using the HD-marketing.com Web site, you consent to the collection, storage, and dissemination of personal data as described above. We will post any changes to our privacy policy on this page so you can readily review the most current policy. HD-marketing.com reserves the right to e-mail you regarding changes to our privacy policy or any other matters HD-marketing.com considers necessary for the administration of the site.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, delete or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page or by [**Contacting Us**] or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

  7. How to Contact Us

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by sending us a message on our **Contact Us** form or by using the following contact information:
